I wish you could all be inside my head.
The conversation is sparkling.
Fine, I'll tell you.
A lichen is an organism made up of two separate species,
fungi and algae.
If you could merge with another species,
what species would you pick and why?
Hint: There is a right answer.
None of you will get it.
Okay, I'd pick swan because,
uh, the resulting hybrid would have
the advanced industrial civilization of a human
and the long graceful neck I've always dreamed of having.
Wrong. Leonard?
Horse, but mostly just for the height.
A little bit for the genital girth.
Wrong, and let's keep it clean, shall we?
Kangaroo, uh,
I'd be Kanga-Jew.
The first of my people to dunk a basketball.
Also instead of just living in your mother's house,
you could actually live inside her body.
Clever, but also wrong.
No, the best organism for human beings to merge with
is the lichen itself.
That way, you'd be human, fungus, and algae.
Triple threat.
Like three-bean salad.
Give me one circumstance in which that would be useful.
All right, picture this:
a beautiful outdoor concert.
Now, as a human, I appreciate Beethoven.
As a fungus, I have a terrific view,
growing out of a towering maple tree.
And no thank you, expensive concessions.
Because as an algae, I'll just snack on this sunlight.
- He got us again. - No, he didn't.
Anyway, if it's okay with you,
we should talk about Howard's bachelor party.
Seems like a bit of a letdown
after our lichen conversation, but...
what do you know, you're half swan.
I've been doing some research on strippers.
One agency I spoke to, said I could get us a great price
if we're flexible on age range and number of limbs.
Sounds like loads of fun,
but I promised Bernadette no strippers.
You don't want strippers?
You're the king of strippers.
The one club in North Hollywood
named a pole after you.
What can I tell ya, I'm not into that stuff anymore.
Good for you, Howard. I'm proud of you.
And still, you're the first one of use to get married.
We have to do something special.
You know Germans have an interesting pre-wedding custom--
Well, it's probably not for me.
Maybe we can go up to Napa Valley.
They've got that wine train.
Boo, wine!
But yay, trains. I'm in.
Anyway, it's a beautiful time of year.
Uh, you travel through the vineyards.
There's a tasting on board.
And all the wildflowers are in bloom.
Magic.
Look at that, in 30 seconds,
we went from hiring women to being them.
So, I hear you and the lost boys
are having a bachelor party tonight.
Yeah, just going to a restaurant,
get some steaks, and scotch.
- Nothing to worry about. - Why should I worry?
Well, I don't know. It's a bachelor party.
There could be strippers.
Wouldn't that make you a little jealous?
Oh, come on Leonard, it's you. What's going to happen?
I mean, even if there was a stripper,
all you'd do is avoid eye-contact
and maybe offer to help her kid with his homework.
Hey, I am a young man in his sexual prime.
Under the right conditions, I-I-I am capable of just,
really crazy stuff.
Really? What is the craziest thing
you've ever done with a woman?
And the time you and I had sex in the ocean does not count.
Oh, come on. That's got to count.
There was a really strong undertow, we could have died.
Well, have fun tonight.
Oh, I will.
There is no telling what might happen.
Yeah, there is.
You know, there's nothing wrong helping some woman's kid
get through their S.A.T.'s.
Hey, I got to hand it to Raj,
he found a really nice spot to have a bachelor party.
It's not bad.
Unless you compare it to a train; then it stinks.
Are you drinking whiskey?
Indeed.
If I'm to participate in the social convention
that is the stag night,
then I must embrace all its components:
including tobacco, swear words,
and yes, alcohol.
Jeepers! That's yucky.
Whoa, it's a little early to start
dropping J-bombs, don't you think?
- Hey, you guys. - Oh, hey, Wil.
Nice of you to make it out tonight for Howard.
Well, it was either this or another
hot tub party at George Takei's house.
I'm confused.
I thought since our reconciliation,
I was your friend in this group.
Oh, I'm friends with Howard too.
I guess you're just friends with anybody.
Hey, uh, Leonard...
things are a little tight at the comic book store.
I might need some help covering my share of the check.
Oh, yeah, no worries.
And maybe a few bucks for the valet.
Oh, all right.
And gas money to get home.
- Yeah, sure. - Great.
You know what? This is my grandfather's watch.
18-carat gold, got it in Europe during the war.
Wow, that's very nice. Mm-hmm.
100 bucks and it's yours.
Hey, everybody!
The bachelor boy has arrived!
* For he's a jolly good fellow *
* Which nobody can deny *
Yes, yes, yes. He's a jolly good fellow.
What time do the strippers arrive?
Actually, Barry, we're not going to have strippers tonight.
Ah, then what the frig did I get 200 dollars in singles out for?
You want to buy a watch?
This is Maid of Honor Amy Farrah Fowler,
bringing you the wedding activities
just weeks out from the big day.
Let's check in with a beautiful, radiant young woman,
and her friend who's about to get married.
Ladies, can you tell us what you're doing?
Um, these are gift bags
we're going to put in the hotel rooms of our out-of-town guests.
This is a map of Pasadena.
This is a list of local restaurants.
And then, for Howie's relatives,
we have antihistamines, antacids,
and medicine for diarrhea and constipation.
Yeah, we labeled them "stop and go."
All right, pivoting to the big question:
Bernadette, on your wedding night
you'll be consummating your marriage.
What do you think your first sexual position will be
as husband and wife?
Amy, please.
Keeping in mind that whoever's on top
may set the tone for the marriage.
Okay, show's over.
Hey, they may conceive a child on their wedding night.
Don't you think the kid might get a kick
out of knowing how it happened?
I don't care.
Ask her things like "Are you going to take Howard's name?"
Not "Who's going to sit on who."
I've actually been thinking I'm going to hyphenate:
Bernadette Maryann Rostenkowski-Wolowitz.
Nice.
You know, you should totally get
Bernadette Maryann Rostenkowski-Wolowitz.com
before someone snaps it up.
Howard already took care of it.
Plus, he set up our beautiful wedding Web site
with cute little facts about our family histories.
Do you know, for a while in Poland,
my family and his family were neighbors.
Oh, that's cool.
No, it's not. I'll explain it to you later.
May I have your attention, please?
We are here tonight to celebrate the upcoming nuptials
of my best friend Howard Wolowitz.
Hear! Hear!
And, apparently, Wil Wheaton's best friend.
Sheldon...
Talk to the hand.
Does anyone have any words
they'd like to say about our man of the evening?
I do.
As is the tradition,
I have prepared a series of disrespectful jokes
which generate humor at Howard's expense.
Prepare to have your ribs tickled...
Howard...
I always thought you'd be the last one of us to ever get married,
because you are so short and unappealing.
Am I right?
Let's see here.
Oh, seriously though, Howard,
you're actually one of the most intelligent people I know.
And that's a zinger, because you're not.
I've always thought that you'd make
someone a fine husband someday.
Assuming you'd be able to get the parts,
and develop the engineering skills
to assemble them, which I don't see as likely.
Hacha!
Okay... Let me see here.
Okay, kidding aside--
Howard, you are a good friend.
And I wish you nothing but happiness.
Bazinga, I don't!
- Sheldon... - Double bazinga! I do!
Good luck following that.
So, Howard Wolowitz tying the knot.
Leaving his crazy bachelor days behind.
He was a wild one.
Well, I guess we all kind of were.
I remember this one time,
I was with this girl at the beach.
We were in the ocean and we started making out.
I know, it was crazy.
I wasn't even wearing my Aquasocks.
Then...
Nobody cares, Hofstadter.
Wrap it up.
Right.
To Howard.
I totally had sex in the ocean.
Okay, I'll go.
Howard, when I think about you and Bernadette
starting this wonderful life together,
I can't help but get a little choked up.
I mean...
look at you.
You have everything.
Look at me.
I'm 37.
I sleep in the back of a comic book store,
and I have the bone density of an 80-year-old man.
To Howard.
- Um, uh, who's next?  - I'll go.
Howard, I'm gonna say something to you that everybody's thinking
but no one has the courage to say out loud.
When you invite a man to a bachelor party,
the implication is, there will be strippers.
Maybe not completely nude,
but at least pasties and G-strings.
That's not unreasonable.
- Hear, hear.  - Hear, hear.
Okay, uh, anybody else?
Huh? No?
Okay, it all comes down to me, the best man.
Ooh! This grasshopper is kicking my ass-hopper.
Okay, okay, when I first came to this country,
I-I didn't know how to behave or how to dress,
or what was cool...I was pretty lonely.
But then I met Howard,
and suddenly, my life changed,
because we could be lonely together.
This man became my whole world.
Yeah, nice speech, Francine.
I'm not done, but thank you.
I think back....
...to all the good times we had, like, uh,
when we went camping and spent that night
telling each other all our secrets.
I told him I'm addicted to pedicures
and he told me he lost his virginity to his cousin.
She was my second cousin.
And the first woman you ever disappointed sexually.
Ba-da-bazinga!
Oh...oh, yeah, and then there was the time
when Leonard and I took Howard to Las Vegas
and paid a hooker to pretend she was Jewish
and that she wanted his little kosher pickle.
Of all the "Howard humping hookers" stories,
that one's my favorite!
Okay, buddy, that's it. Sit down.
Oh, oh, what about that tubby girl
in the Sailor Moon costume at Comic-con?
Don't remember. Please sit down.
The only threesome I've ever had in my life,
and I'm proud to say it was with this man right here.
Oh, please shut up.
Oh, oh, don't get me wrong,
nothing happened with me and Howard.
There was about 200 pounds of Sailor Moon between us.
Oh, Internet, this is so going all over you.
Jeepers, I'm drunk.
Thank you for picking us up.
There's a warning, right there, on the scotch bottle.
You cannot be operatin' heavy machinery
after you had a snootful of this, laddie!
Funny.
You boys have a nice time?
Yeah, it was great.
Low-key, like I promised.
No hanky-panky, no strippers.
Just the guys telling jokes.
That's nice.
How about you? Did you have a fun night?
Yeah, we, uh, made gift bags, had wine,
and then went online and saw this.
Of all the "Howard humping hookers" stories,
that one's my favorite.
You know, we're not that far from my apartment.
If you stop the car, I can walk from here.
You ain't goin' anywhere, Threeway.
- Bernadette, listen...  - You lied to me.
You said you told me about all the girls you've been with,
but you never mentioned your cousin,
the prostitute or Raj!
Seriously, you don't even have to stop the car.
Anything under ten miles an hour
and I can combat-roll into the street.
Okay, just to set the record straight,
I didn't hire the prostitute, she was a gift from him.
Shame on you, Raj.
That is not how we treat women in this country.
Don't you try and blame this on him.
- Thank you, Bernadette.  - Zip it, pervert!
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'm supposed to marry Howard in a couple weeks
and I'm not sure I even know who the man is anymore.
I'm curious what's bothering you most:
the borderline incest, the prostitute
or group sex with the girl dressed as the children's cartoon?
Amy, remember when we went over things
that would be helpful and things that wouldn't?
Right.
- And that was... - Not.
When I first met Howard, he seemed so innocent to me,
just a sweet little guy who lives with his mother.
Well, if that's what you like,
I'll take you to the comic book store--
the place is full of 'em.
Wait a minute.
You set me up with Howard.
Did you know about all the creepy stuff he was into?
Well, a little. You hear stuff...
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, I was gonna, but I didn't think
it would go past the first date.
Then, when it did, I thought for sure
it wouldn't go past you meeting his mother.
Definitely not past the two of you sleeping together.
I mean, the warning signs were there--
this is really on you.
God!
I thought you were my friend.
I don't think that was helpful.
Hi, Bernie, it's me again.
Please call me back.
Dude, I am so sorry.
It's not your fault, it's mine.
I did all that stuff, not you.
Actually, you did do one of them together.
Here.
What is this?
You're upset.
The convention is to bring an upset person a hot beverage.
No, but what is it?
Chicken broth.
It seemed culturally appropriate.
Also, there was a single cube of chicken bouillon
in the cupboard when I moved in
and it's been bothering me for the last eight years...
So, as they say, two birds.
I don't know what my next move is.
Well, Howard, I don't know much about women...
- Yeah? - No, uh, that, that's it.
I don't know much about women.
Raj, you got anything?
I've got the phone number of the tubby girl from Comic-Con.
I'm not calling the girl from Comic-con.
All right.
More Sailor Moon for me.
I just threw up the bachelor party.
Please come out, Bernadette.
Let's talk through this.
No, leave me alone.
Perhaps you should give him a taste of his own medicine.
Do you have a cousin who you find attractive?
Amy.
Hey, you introduced her to the sleazebag.
I'm just trying to clean up your mess.
I need to talk to Bernadette.
Well, I don't think she wants to talk to anyone right now.
All right, well, could you at least give her a message?
Yeah, sure, I guess.
Tell her I'm really sorry.
And if she doesn't want to marry me, I get it.
But what I really want her to know
is the guy that she's disgusted by,
is the guy that I'm disgusted by, too.
But that guy doesn't exist anymore; he's gone.
And the reason is because of her.
So, if this relationship is over,
let her know that she made me a better man,
and tell her thank you.
Oh, my God, Howard.
That's the most beautiful thing I've ever heard.
And it came out of you.
Howie?
Penny has a message for you.
I heard.
Your voice, not unlike your mother's,
travels through walls.
Do you want me to go?
No.
Come here.
I'm still really mad at you.
I get that.
Is there anything else about your past I should know?
Couple things, but, you know, most of them happened overseas.
I'll tell you later.
Okay.
So, is the wedding still on?
Yeah, the wedding's still on.
Oh, thank God.
I'm still a maid of honor!
Oh, what the hell.
This is kind of hot.
What's with the robe?
I'm gonna have sex with you right here,
right now, on that washing machine.
No, you're not.
Come on, please.
If you want to do something,
you can help me fold this sheet.
Folding a sheet in my underwear, still pretty crazy.